Léo RASPAUD

SYDNEY - AUSTRALIA - +61 438 228 078

HTTPS://LEORASPAUD.COM

LEO.RASPAUD@GMAIL.COM

Front end lead engineer, passion for JS, back end enthusiast. serverless addict

PROFILE

I am a senior software engineer with good knowledge of front-end techniques and many years of full stack development.

I like every aspect of developing an application, creating a great user experience and a clean code is always a priority for me.

I also like to work on personal projects when I have the time, I'm currently working with ReactJS / NodeJS / AWS

SKILLS



























STRENGTHS

- Leader
- Creative
- Listener
- Team worker
- Quick learner

EDUCATION

2009-2011 Master degree Industrial automation and system engineering 2006-2009 Electronic, electrotechnics, automatic engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior full stack engineer

VoiceFoundry | Since 2021/01 - 📸 Sydney

Working in a team of 9 developpers in Australia and Indonesia. We build and deploy applications using React / NodeJS on AWS.

Senior full stack engineer

Gorgias| 2020/07 - 2020/10 - 👯 Sydney

I currently work in a team of engineers between france, australia and USA. My focus is mainly on the front-end part of the application, developping new features and improving the react application.

Senior full stack engineer

Athena | 2018/11 - 2020/06 - 🁯 Sydney

Working in a team of 6 senior developers. As a full stack engineer I'm working on both back-end and front-end. I mainly work on new features of the react application, bug fixing and various improvements.

Chief Technology Officer (CTO)

Nod | 2017/08 - 2018/11 - ₹ Sydney

In charge of the software engineering team of Nod. My job is to manage the engineering team as well as developing the product and finding the best solutions to improve our product. I manage a team of 5 full stack engineer and 3 data scientists. As a CTO in a startup I spend most of my time writing code and mentoring our software engineers. I also do regular workshops to make sure everyone has the same skills.

Front-end lead engineer

Dexstr | 2016/01 - 2017/08 - | Toulouse

Development of new functionalities (AngularJS 1.6 / Java 8) Task automation (Gulp)

UI/UX improvements (Angular Material, HTML, CSS, postCSS) Deployment management (Jenkins, AWS, Docker) In charge of the frontend part of our application, my job is to design and develop the new features to improve our product.

I also like to take time to check the quality of the code and take full responsibility regarding the new frameworks that we may use.

Full stack engineer

Decasoft | 2014/10 - 2015/12 - Toulouse

Development of an internal reporting tool for Decasoft using a MEAN stack (MongoDB, ExpressJS, AngularJS, NodeJS) in complete

I also worked as a consultant for a french hospital and worked with Java / GWT in an agile TDD environment.

Full stack engineer

Capgemini | 2011/04 - 2014/10 - 🕕 Toulouse

Web applications JAVA / Oracle / Struts Maintenance under operational conditions (SH, PL/SQL) Technical solutions estimation / Design of technical solutions / Deployments (Jenkins / SH)